Guide to the Historic Ephemera Collection 1880-2016
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- Organizations
  - Grange (Patrons of Husbandry) -- Washington State
    - "Your Washington State Grange." Pamphlet.
    - "Deputy Conference." Program. Roosevelt Hotel, Seattle, WA. Washington State Grange. 1977.
  - Women's Clubs
    - Idaho
      - Idaho State Federation of Women's Clubs. Biennial year books, 1922-1924, 1928-1929.
      - Fifteenth Annual Meeting of the Idaho Third District Federation of Women's Clubs. Lewiston, ID. 1916 October.
      - The Questers. Program for 1926-1927.
    - Illinois
      - Chicago Woman's Shelter and Annex. Brochure. Circa 1916.
    - Oregon
      - W. C. T. U. Calendar. State Women's Christian Temperance Union of Oregon. [1904?]
      - Official Call and Program, Seventeenth Annual Meeting. Oregon Federation of Women's Clubs. Prineville. 1917 October 22-25.
      - The Fortnightly Club of Eugene, Oregon. 1918-1919.
      - Oregon City Woman's Club. 1921-1922.
      - Annual Program of the Woman's Missionary Society and Woman's Association. Portland. 1919-1920.
      - Chapter A: Twentieth Annual Year Book. Portland. 1924-1925.
      - Portland Woman's Club. 25th Annual Announcement. 1921-1922.
    - Washington State
      - Instructions to Delegates: to Fifteenth Annual Convention of Washington State Federation of Women's Clubs. Brochure. 1911.
      - Official Call to the Thirty-Seventh Annual Meeting of the Washington State Federation of Women's Clubs. Spokane. 1933 June.
      - Twenty-Third Annual Convention of the Washington State Federation of Women's Clubs. Program. Centralia. 1919 June.
      - Washington State Chapter: P.E.O. Twenty-Third Annual Convention. Minutes. Bellingham. 1926 June 9.
      - Washington State Federation of Women's Clubs Directory. 1950-1951.
      - Washington State Federation of Women's Clubs. Third Annual Meeting. Seattle. 1899 June.
      - P.L.F. Year Book. Bellingham. 1910-1911.
      - P.L.F. Year Book. Bellingham. 1927-1928.
      - Triangle Club. Brewster. 1940-1941.
      - Woman's Commercial Club. Castle Rock. 1926-1927.
      - Northeastern District Federation of Women's Clubs Year Book. Cheney. 1927-1928.
      - Music Study Club of Clarkston, Washington. 1926-1927.
      - Sacajawea Club: Nineteenth Annual Announcement. Clarkston. 1926-1927.
      - Aloha Club Year Book. Colfax. 1934-1935.
      - The Athenaeum Club Year Book. Colfax. 1896-1903; 1930-1931 (8 items).
      - Elizabeth Forrest-Day Club. Dayton. 1933-1934.
      - The Everett Woman's Club. Program. 1926-1927.
      - Thirty-Fourth Annual Announcement of the Woman's Book Club. Everett. 1927-1928.
      - Woman's Club Year Book. Hoquiam. 1928-1929.
      - Year Book of the Woman's Club. Neppel. 1926-1927.
      - Woman's Club of Olympia. Olympia. 1963-1964.
      - Woman's Literacy Club Program. Port Angeles. 1928-1929.
      - Prosser Woman's Club. Prosser. 1939-1940.
      - Daughters of the American Revolution: Eliza Hart Spalding Chapter. Pullman. 1923-1924, 1924-1925, 1936-1937, 1937-1938, 1938-1939, 1940-1941, 1943-1944.
      - Pullman Women's Council. 1914-1915.
      - Pullman Mother's Club. 1914-1915, 1916-1917, 1917-1918 (2 copies), 1918-1919, 1919-1920, 1920-1921 (2 copies).
      - Pullman Woman's Club. 1923-1924, 1925-1926, 1926-1927, 1927-1928, 1928-1929, 1929-1930, 1930-1931.
      - Pullman Women's Club. 1931-1932, 1932-3, 1933-4, 1934-1935, 1935-1936, 1937-1938, 1938-1939, 1947-1948.
      - Websterian Debating Society, Ninth Annual Banquet. Pullman. 1909 May 12.
      - Year Book of the Puyallup Woman's Club. Puyallup. 1910-1911.
      - Research Club. Raymond. 1929-1930.
      - The Reardan Women's Club. 1926-1927.
      - Rosalia Study Club Program. 1927-1928.
      - Classic Culture Club. Seattle. 1928-1929.
      - Ladies Grotto Club. Seattle. 1927-1928.
      - Sorosis Year Book. Seattle. 1911-1912.
      - The Seattle Foundation of Women's Clubs. 1928-1929.
      - The Woman's Century Club. Seattle. 1927-1928, 1928-1929.
      - Woman's Educational Club. (Seattle) 1928-1929.
      - The Woman's Century Club. Seattle. 1928-1929.
      - Women's University Club of Seattle. 1928-1929.
      - Women's University Club of Seattle. 1924-1925.
      - Women's University Club of Seattle. 1921-1922.
      - The Women's Century Club. Seattle. 1922-1923.
      - Progressive Club. Sequim. 1926.
      - Snohomish District Federation of Women's Clubs Directory. 1926-1927.
      - Wednesday Club Year Book. Spokane. 1928-1929, 1929-1930, 1930-1931.
      - The Amethyst Club. Spokane. 1926-1927.
      - Spokane Sorosis. 1926-1927.
      - Fortnightly Study Club Year Book. Spokane. 1926-1927.
      - Twentieth Century Club Year Book. Spokane. 1926-1927.
      - The Spokane Federation of Women's Organizations. Spokane. 1930-1931.
      - The Woman's Club of Spokane. Spokane, WA. 1920-1911.
      - The Spokane Federation of Women's Organizations. Spokane. 1926-1927.
      - Year Book of the Sumner Civic Improvement Club. Sumner. 1928-1929.
      - Athena Club. Tacoma. 1926-1927, 1932-1933, 1939-1940, 1940-1941, 1941-1942.
      - Illahee Study Club. Tacoma. 1927-1928.
      - Illema Club. Tacoma. 1928-1929.
      - The Woman's Club Year Book. Tacoma. 1928-1929.
      - Woman's Club Program. Toledo. 1926-1927.
      - Waitsburg Amity Art Club. Waitsburg. 1929-1930, 1931-1932.
      - Progressive Club Year Book. Waitsburg. 1939-1940, 1941-1942.
      - Washington State Federation of Women's Clubs. Badge. Walla Walla. 1938.
      - Woman's Reading Club. Walla Walla. 1911-1912.
      - Woman's Club. White Bluffs. 1927-1928.
      - The White Salmon Woman's Club. White Salmon. 1928-1928.
  - Other
    - "Washington Children's Home Finder." Washington Children's Home Society. Vol. 19, No. 6. Seattle, WA. 1916 July.
    - "United Black Congress First Annual Banquet." Program. November 11, 1977. Washington State University.
  - Unsorted Items
- Places (also see Travel)
  - Postcards
    - Amsterdam, Holland
    - Miscellaneous postcards
    - British Columbia
  - Europe
    - Europe Road Atlas.
    - Denmark
      - Odense Bys Museer (City of Odense Museums). 1960.
    - England
      - The Crown Jewels in the Tower of London. 1962.
      - The Tower of London. 1967.
      - Hampton Court Palace. 1967.
      - A Visitor's Guide to London in 1959. The Barclays Group of Banks.
    - Germany
      - The Rhine: Heart of Europe. 1958.
      - Reihnfalz. Schwarz-Bildbücher.
      - Heidelberg map.
    - Italy
      - You in Venice. Guidebook. 1967.
      - Pisa: Monuments of the "Miracle's Square." Prof. M. F. Carlesi. Guidebook. 1966.
      - Isola Bella. Guidebook.
      - Palermo. Italian State Tourist Department. 1937.
      - Vicenzia. ENIT. 1937.
      - Umbria. Italian State Tourist Department. 1937.
    - Monaco
      - Principauté de Monaco.
    - The Netherlands (Holland)
      - This is Holland. Picture book.
      - Keukenhof Lisse Holland. Picture book.
      - Rijksmuseum, Amsterdam. Art book.
  - North America
    - Canada
      - "Vancouver Visitors' Fun Map." Greater Vancouver Tourist Association.
      - Vancouver Island. Pamphlet about Vancouver, B.C.
      - Who Makes What in British Columbia and Where Obtainable. Vancouver, B.C. 1914.
      - "Canada's Evergreen Playground, 6-Days Tours." Canadian Pacific. 1936.
    - United States
      - Alaska
        - "Mt. McKinley, Alaska." Brochure.
      - California
        - "Party Wine Punches and Wine Cocktails." Italian Swiss Colony. General Offices: San Francisco.
        - "San Francisco Hotel Greeters Guide." 1948 April.
      - Idaho
        - J and F National Profit-Sharing Coupon, Rankin's Store. Viola, ID.
        - "Clark House On Hayden Lake, F. Lewis Clark Mansion." Leaflet.
        - "Let's Establish A National Historical Park In North Central Idaho!" Leaflet. Nez Perce Country National Historical Park Association.
        - "Moose Creek Ranch." Brochure. Orofino, ID.
        - "Idaho Recreation Guide." Leaflet.
        - Idaho: the place to go in 1976. Idaho Innkeepers Association. Centennial year brochure for hotels and restaurants.
        - "Idaho Bicentennial 1776-1976: Events Vacation 1976."
        - Sun Valley, Idaho. Pamphlet. Circa 1940s.
        - Sun Valley, Idaho: Summer. Pamphlet. Circa 1940s.
        - Ford Time. Booklet of essays. Orville Lowe, Inc. Des Moines, Ia. 1954. (Note: features article and clippings on Skyline Drive.)
        - Cottonwood
          - "Sixty-six Years of Service: 1884-1950." Sister M. Alfreda Elsensohn. Pamphlet. The Sisters of St. Gertrude's Community, St. Gertrude's Convent. Cottonwood, ID.
          - "Seventy-Five Years of Service: 1884-1959, Fifty Years at Cottonwood: 1909-1959." Sister M. Alfreda Elsensohn. Pamphlet. The Sisters of St Gertrude's Community, St. Gertrude's Convent. Cottonwood, ID. 2 copies.
        - Latah County
          - "Historic Latah County, Idaho." Brochure. Moscow, ID. Circa 1975.
          - Book cover advertising Moscow, ID businesses. American Book Covers, Inc. 1953.
        - Lewiston
          - "Souvenir Folder of North and South Highway and Lewiston Spiral." Lewiston, ID.
      - Kansas
        - Fac-Simile of Confederate 10-dollar bill. (Coupon for Lawrence Business College, Lawrence, KS.)
      - Louisiana
        - Historical Wax Museum of New Orleans: Musée Conti. Souvenir Guide Book. 1964.
      - Maine
        - Greater Portland: A Pleasure Guide for Visitors. Portland, ME. Volume 4, Number 2. 1960 July 15.
      - Montana
        - "An Acre in Montana Is Worth More Than an Acre Elsewhere." Flyer.
        - Experience the Nez Perce Trail. Auto Tour pamphlet, Yellowstone National Park to Canyon Creek, MT, 2011.
        - Glacier Park Boat Company. Information card with schedule and prices. Kalispell, MT.
      - New York
        - Visitors Guide to New York: the Greatest All Year Round Vacation City. Brochure. Circa 1946-1950.
        - Empire Observatories souvenir ticket.
      - North Dakota
        - Bottineau, North Dakota. Brochure.
        - Why Not Minot, North Dakota: Continental Crossroads. Brochure.
        - Garrison Dam and Reservoir. Brochure. Riverdale, ND. 1963.
      - Oregon
        - "The Round-Up." Leaflet. Pendleton, OR. Sept. 18-21, 1929.
        - "Mt. Hood Stages Inc. Time Tables." Leaflet.
        - "The One and Only Sea Lion Caves." Leaflet. Florence, OR.
        - "You'll Find a Friendly, Prosperous Country." Leaflet. Wallowa County, OR.
        - Our Boys. Woodburn, OR. 1932 December; 1933 December.
        - "Lend a Hand." Inmates of the Oregon Penitentiary. Vol. 17, No. 6. 1921 November.
        - "Lend a Hand." Inmates of the Oregon Penitentiary. Vol. 18, No. 6. 1922 November.
        - "The Mayor's Address." City of Portland. Municipal Year 1879-1880.
        - "Celebrities--Portland Greeters." Newsletter. 1919.
        - "Pendleton Round-Up." Official Souvenir Program. Pendleton, OR. 1925. (Location note: in Oversize 1)
        - "Vot's To Do at Timberline!" Leaflet. Timberline Lodge. Government Camp, OR. 1964.
        - Corvallis
          - "Welcome to Corvallis: Hotel-Motel Directory." Brochure. Corvallis Chamber of Commerce.
          - Map of Corvallis and Oregon State Campus. 1964.
      - Pacific Northwest
        - "Map of Pacific Highway: Oregon and Washington." Waverly Oil Dealers brochure.
        - "Grays Harbor Lines, Motor Coach Service." Leaflet. 1939 February 1.
        - "Longview Bridge: the Short Route Over the Columbia River." Oregon and Washington.
        - "Outings in the Pacific Northwest." 1936?
        - What People Do on a Dude Ranch. Pamphlet. Northern Pacific, Yellowstone Park Line.
        - Ranch Vacations. Pamphlet. Northern Pacific, Yellowstone Park Line.
        - "White Pass and Yukon Route, Alaska and the Yukon." Season 1939. Brochure.
        - North Pacific Fair Circuit--Harness Race Schedule. Oregon-Washington-Idaho-British Columbia. 1911.
      - Washington, D.C.
        - Brief Guide to the Smithsonian Institution. Pamphlet, eighth edition.
        - Beautiful Washington D.C., Our Nation's Capital, in Natural Color. Pamphlet. 1950.
      - Washington State
        - "What Does a Vacation Mean to You?" Brochure. American River Resort, Snoqualmie National Forest. Naches, WA.
        - "isn't it time we had a...Palouse Conservation Program?" Brochure.
        - "McNary Lock and Dam, Lake Wallula." Columbia River, Oregon and Washington. U.S. Army Corps of Engineers brochure, 1987.
        - The Hanford Story. Pamphlet. 1969.
        - Fait's Pacific Northwest Guide. 1939-1940.
        - Facts About Washington State. Pamphlet. Department of Commerce and Economic Development. Olympia, WA. 1958 January.
        - The New Washington State. Pamphlet. Washington State Planning Council. Olympia, WA. 1943 July.
        - "State of Washington, Department of Highways Official Map." Olympia. 1933.
        - The Washington State Capitol Group. Pamphlet. Washington State Progress Commission. Circa 1942.
        - "Washington State's Spirit Lake Memorial Highway (SR 504)." Brochure and map. 1988.
        - "Exposition." Program. Works Progress Administration, District No. 4. 1936 May 15.
        - Program for dedication of historical marker and observance of 100th anniversary of Monticello Territorial Convention Centennial. Longview, WA. Washington State Parks and Recreation Commission. 1952 November 25.
        - "White Pass." Brochure. Chehalis, WA. Circa 1930s.
        - "Why Washington Needs More Safe Highways." Brochure. Portland Cement Association. Circa 1930s.
        - "Keep Washington Green and Build for the Future." Address by Dr. Wilson Compton. 1945.
        - "Washington On Parade: Golden Jubilee, 1889-1939." Brochure. Seattle, WA. 1939. 2 copies.
        - The Ordeal of the Steptoe Command. Pamphlet. Randall A. Johnson. Signed by author. 1972.
        - "The Story of the Petrified Forest (Gingko State Park, Washington)." State Parks and Recreation Commission pamphlet. 1952.
        - "White Pass-White Bluffs Cross-State Highway." Flyer. Circa 1930s-1940s.
        - The Washington Spectator. Vol. 1, No. 2. July, 1937.
        - Two Fusulinids from the Granite Falls Limestone. Roy A. Anderson. Conference presentation (typescript), "N.W.S. in Spokane," 1936 December.
        - "The 'Alps of America' Invite You to Big 4 Inn and Scenic Monte Cristo Region." Brochure.
        - "Mount St. Helens." Mount St. Helens Geological Area. U.S. Department of Agriculture. Includes packet of ash. (Location note: in Oversize 1)
        - "Travel Guide to State Parks Evergreen Playgrounds." Single leaf. Circa 1940s.
        - "Summer of '74." The Magazine of Northwest Summer Recreation. KBIQ. Seattle. 1974.
        - Asotin County
          - "A Desirable Place to Live." Pamphlet. Asotin County, WA. Circa 1930. (2 copies)
        - Bainbridge Island
          - "The Playground of Seattle invites YOU." Brochure. Bainbridge Island Central Committee.
        - Bremerton
          - Fight On The Home Front With Bremerton Navy Yard. Pamphlet. 1943.
        - Centralia
          - "Centralia, Washington: General Data and Information." Brochure.
          - "Centralia Steam-Electric Project." Brochure. 1971.
        - Chehalis
          - "Constitution and By-Laws of the Southwest Washington Settlers' Agency." Pamphlet. Chehalis, WA. Circa 1910s.
          - "Chehalis: the friendly city." Brochure. Chehalis and Lewis County.
          - "Empire of Vacation Dreams: Southwest Washington." Brochure.
          - "Chehalis: The Friendly City." Brochure. Chehalis Chamber of Commerce.
          - "History of Chehalis and Lewis County." Mrs. Charles Mitchell, excerpt from her manuscript, "Early History of Chehalis and Lewis County." Chehalis Chamber of Commerce. (Location note: oversize 1)
        - Cheney
          - "Cheney, Washington: City of Industries, Homes and Schools." Brochure.
        - Chewelah
          - "Chewelah, Stevens County, Washington." Brochure. Chewelah Chamber of Commerce. 1941.
        - Colville
          - "Colville: The Center of The Upper Columbia Empire." Brochure. Colville Chamber of Commerce. Circa 1940s.
          - "Outdoor Life In the Scenic Colville Country." Brochure. Colville Chamber of Commerce. Circa 1940s.
        - Dayton
          - The S.O.L. Newspaper (parody). Volume 7. Dayton, WA. 1926 November 11. (Location note: Oversize 2)
        - Everett
          - Trade extension warrants in the denominations of blank, one, five, and ten dollars, stamped "Void." Circa 1933. (4 items.)
        - Hanford
          - "Proud of Hanford" bumper sticker.
        - King County
          - "History and Progress of King County, Washington." 1916. (Location note: In Oversize 1)
        - Kittitas County
          - "Port of Kittitas County." Pamphlet. Circa 1969.
        - Lake Chelan
          - "General Information About Lake Chelan." Brochure. Circa 1948-1950.
          - "The Moore Inn on Beautiful Lake Chelan." Leaflet.
          - "Lake Chelan: Fisherman's Mecca." Leaflet. Circa 1930s.
          - "Lake Chelan." Brochure.
        - Long Beach
          - "Vacation at Long Beach, Washington." Brochure. Circa 1950.
        - Longview
          - "Longview, Washington." Map.
        - Moses Lake
          - "Neppel Moses Lake District, Washington." Pamphlet. Chicago, Milwaukee, St. Paul Railway. 1913 November.
          - Zoning Ordinance. Pamphlet. Moses Lake. 1945.
          - Building Code. Pamphlet. Moses Lake. 1945.
          - "Moses Lake: A Name In Your Future." Leaflet. Moses Lake Chamber of Commerce. 1951.
        - Okanogan County
          - "Commercial Bank, 1890-1920." Pamphlet. Okanogan. 2 copies.
        - Olympic Peninsula
          - "Carl Cooper's Pacific Beach Hotel: Gay and Lazy Days." Brochure.
          - "Scenic Auto-Ferry Route Between Seattle and Olympic Peninsula." Leaflet. Ballard-Ludlow Ferry Co. 2 copies.
          - "The Quinault." Hotel advertising flyer. 1937.
          - "The Fourth Annual Trout Derby and Barbecue: Lake Quinault." Program. 1939 May 28.
          - "Olympic Peninsula Resort and Hotel Information." Pamphlet. 1939.
          - "Olympic Hot Springs Mountain Resort." Brochure. 2 versions.
          - "Land of Olympus...Playfield of the Gods." Brochure. The Olympicans.
          - "Thrill to the Call of the Olympic Wilderness." Brochure. The Olympicans.
          - "Olympic National Park, Washington." Leaflet. National Park Concessions, Inc.
        - Othello
          - "Mar Don Resort on Potholes Reservoir." Brochure. Othello, WA. Circa 1970s-1980s.
        - Palouse
          - "A Walking Tour of Historic Palouse." Brochure.
        - Pend Oreille County
          - "Pend Oreille County, Washington." Brochure. (2 copies)
          - "Official Opening: Pend Oreille River Bridge at USK." Leaflet. Washington State Department of Highways. 1964 July 11.
        - Pullman
          - Pullman Cab Co. advertising card.
          - City of Pullman: Traffic, Vehicles, and Pets. Pamphlet. Circa 1970s.
          - Know Your City: Pullman. Pamphlet. 1968.
          - Pullman: Home of Washington State University. Brochure with map. Circa 1960s.
          - Three Forks Press. Volume 1, Number 2. April 13, Year One. (Location note: Oversize 2)
          - Central Business District Development: Pullman. Pamphlet. 1968 October.
          - "Summer Clearance Sale." Flyer. Blackman Bros. and Co. (Location note: Oversize 1)
          - "Pullman Chamber of Commerce." Brochure. Pullman, WA.
          - "An Invitation to Live in Pullman, the Friendly Town, Home of Washington State College." Circa 1946. (2 copies)
          - Pullman as a College City. Chamber of Commerce brochure. Circa 1926.
          - "A New Hospital." Pullman Community Hospital Corporation. 1976.
          - "Pullman is Different." Pullman Chamber of Commerce.
          - Facts about Pullman, Washington and Whitman County. Pullman Chamber of Commerce. Circa 1970.
          - "Community Hotel, Pullman, Washington." Pamphlet. Circa 1927.
          - The Pullman Holiday Messenger. Pullman, WA. 1919 December-1920 January. (Location note: in Oversize 1)
          - "Pullman, Washington: In the Heart of the World's Richest Wheat Belt." Pamphlet. Pullman Chamber of Commerce. Circa 1950s.
          - "Pullman Dining and Lodging." Pamphlet. Pullman Chamber of Commerce.
          - Christmas Songs. Booklet. JC Penney Co. Pullman, WA. Circa 1930.
          - JC Penney Co. notebook. Pullman.1930.
          - "There is a Difference in Gasoline: Try Fire Chief." (Personalized to Mr. Brewster). Pamphlet. Cougar Service Station. Pullman, WA. Circa 1936.
          - "MJ's Marijuana Menu." Single leaf. 2014. Pullman, WA.
          - A Century of Spirit. Leaflet. United Way of Pullman. 1982.
          - "On the Right Track." Brochure. Pullman Chamber of Commerce. Circa 1986.
          - Footloose in the Palouse: Running and Walking Trails In and Around the Palouse. Brochure. Washington State University.
          - Pullman, Washington: Historic Walking Tour. Pamphlet. Pullman Mainstreet Program and Pullman Chamber of Commerce. 1987.
          - First Annual Banquet of the Pullman Commercial Club. Program and menu. 1909.
        - Rosalia
          - "Steptoe Monument Rededication Program." Steptoe Monument Park, Rosalia, WA. 1958 June 7.
          - "Welcome to Rosalia, Washington." Flyer.
          - "Official Program, Second Annual Rosalia Rodeo." Rosalia, WA. Rosalia Chamber of Commerce. 1950 June 3-4.
        - Seattle
          - Traffic Laws, Rules and Regulations and Washington Toll Bridge Authority. Lake Washington Bridge. Pamphlet. 1940.
          - Traffic Laws, Rules and Regulations and Washington Toll Bridge Authority. Tacoma Narrows Bridge. Pamphlet. 1940.
          - "Downtown Seattle Directory." Brochure and map of businesses. Circa 1960s.
          - "Pacific Logging Congress." Program. 38th Session and 5th Machinery Show. 1947 November 17-19.
          - Who's Who at the Zoo. Gordon R. Newell. Pamphlet. Woodland Park Zoological Gardens, Seattle. 1956.
          - Seattle, Metropolis of the Charmed Land of the American Continent, the Pacific Northwest. Pamphlet. Lowman and Hanford Co., Seattle. Circa 1920s.
          - The Seattle Spirit. Seattle Chamber of Commerce and Commercial Club newsletter. Vol. 3, No. 25. Seattle, WA. 1919 June 19.
          - "Seattle World's Fair." Brochure. Seattle, WA. 1962.
          - Seattle World's Fair brochure with map. (2 versions)
          - To Our Neighbors. Pamphlet. Seattle Housing Authority. 1956.
          - Seattle: the Convention City of the Charmed Land. Pamphlet. Circa 1930s-1940s.
          - Seattle and Puget Sound. Souvenir photograph book.
          - Seattle Statistics. Seattle Chamber of Commerce. 1923 June.
          - "Seattle: the Claremont Apartment Hotel." Leaflet.
          - "Lake Washington Ship Canal; Hiram M. Chittenden Locks." Pamphlet. U.S. Army Engineer District, Seattle. 1959 May.
          - "Washington Toll Bridge Authority: Lake Washington Bridge, Seattle." Brochure. Circa 1938-1939.
          - "Washington Toll Bridge Authority: Lake Washington Bridge, Seattle, and Tacoma Narrows Bridge." Brochure. Circa 1938-1939.
          - "Lake Washington Floating Bridge." Dedication booklet. Seattle, WA. Metropolitan Press. 1940.
          - Souvenir of Seattle, Wash. Photo-gravures. Pamphlet. 1904.
          - Seattle...Its Opportunities and Charm. Seattle Chamber of Commerce pamphlet. Circa 1946-1950s.
          - Pamphlet for the new Sixth and Denny branch of Seattle-First National Bank. Circa 1950s.
          - "Seattle's $2,000,000,000 Program to Keep Production Rolling--And Win the War." Leaflet. Seattle Chamber of Commerce. Circa 1943.